So how much do your parents pay?
- I don't know.
- Of course you do.
I don't.
- I bet it's worth more than my house.
- I bet it's not.
Look, I'm not posh.
- You're so posh!
- I'm not. I'm just well-educated.
And all that education,
where's that gonna go?
What about you? Did you learn anything
apart from your... gymnastics stuff?
Yeah, but... you don't get it.
I've to get up at 5:00 every morning,
train for two hours...
Fuck me! I couldn't do that.
I need my beauty sleep.
Yeah, well, I fall asleep
in school a lot.
- I can't touch that.
- Seriously?
Nope. Can't drink, I can't smoke.
I'm really boring.
- I bought it back in pieces from France.
- Right.
One of these babies can go
right through a man.
- Mark!
- You wanna see it work?
- Really?
- Yeah, you do.
You put it down like this,
you hoist this thing up...
put it back down like that...
you take your arrow...
just lock it in here...
- And you're good to go.
- All right.
- You wanna go?
- No.
- Are you sure? Are you sure? Just take it.
- Mark, stop! I really don't wanna go.
- Mark!
- Just take... Fuck!
Fuck! I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God!
- Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck...
- What's going on with your phone?
- My mum took it.
- Why? Why? What's happened?
- Come in, I'll explain. Be quiet.
- This place is amazing.
- You'd be a natural housebreaker.
Maybe that's what I should do
with my life.
- Oh, fuck!
- You're such a dickhead.
It's fine, it's fine.
It'll pass in a sec.
It doesn't happen as much as it used to.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
That's really sweet.
Can't believe you haven't been
in here before.
- Looks like it could do with a woman's touch.
- Well, I could do with a woman's touch.
Mark...
- I need to talk to you about something.
- In a bit.
So, what happened?
My mum was doing the laundry,
and she found a wrap in my pocket.
She's gone absolutely nuts.
Won't even let me out of the house now.
"You've abused our trust.
What have you become?"
Blah, blah, blah...
Why do you look so pleased?
I thought you weren't answering
'cause you didn't want to talk to me.
I thought I'd been dumped.
I must have rang you about 50 times.
Shift was a bloody nightmare.
Hang on. Just a second.
Mark! Mark!
- Have you been smoking?
- It's just a joss stick.
Look, we're not monsters.
You'll need this to do your homework.
Can I have my phone back, please?
From Kelly?
Sweet.
Look, I know you feel bad
about what happened, but that's...
Give me back my phone!
She stacks shelves in a supermarket.
And that house is a shocking state.
There's rubbish piled up
in a mattress rotting in the garden.
- You went to her mum's house?
- A mother has a right to be concerned.
- Does she give you the drugs?
- I gave them to her.
None of this nonsense was going on
before she came on the scene.
- A friend works at the social services...
- Mark...
There's no sign of the bloody dog.
It must've run off again, jumped the fence.
He won't come for us. Got to call him.
The dog will be back by morning,
he always is.
Mark and I were just discussing
his attitude.
We've got to get the dog back.
We can't have him worrying sheep.
I can't believe in circumstances
like these, with this crisis going on,
you're concerned about sheep.
- This is our son...
- Your son.
I'll go take a walk
and shout for the dog.
Go, I need a minute to get dressed.
I haven't got a social worker.
Just a family care adviser came 'round
a few times, 'cause of my mum's head.
Look...
- I'm gonna go. I'll see you tomorrow.
- Stay.
No, I don't wanna get you
in any more trouble.
- Mark.
- Stay.
Please. Please stay.
Look, it's my birthday tomorrow...
Please?
Look, my mum will definitely be back
when I go out,
so we should find you
a better hiding place.
Mark!
You've got a lot of crap in this bag.
What's that?
- Unlucky charm.
- Throw it away.
- Kelly, you said you'd got rid of it. What...
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I will.
- I'll get rid of it.
- Jesus! And people call me morbid.
I'm sorry.
Want to go to bed?
I'll tell you a secret.
She's sleeping with a guy down the road.
No.
This one time I was halfway to school,
decided against it, came back and...
there they were.
At it.
And you didn't tell your stepdad?
I think he knows.
I guess he's trying
to catch them at it or...
So fucked up.
South America then...
Mexico.
Guacamole.
Guatemala.
And then, Brazil.
I was supposed to compete there.
Rio it is, then.
When should we leave?
God, I'd love that.
Mark...
We weren't careful enough.
I know. I can't believe my mom
found that wrapper in my pocket.
No, not that.
I'm pregnant.
- There's no debate here.
- Why are you being like this?
I need a fag.
You'd have to give that up.
And everything else you like.
Fine, I can do that.
I've done that before.
I've got my whole life to think about...
I've got my future ahead of me.
- What was that?
- Don't try and change the subject.
Is it your mum?
I don't think so.
Mark...
Mark, what are you doing?
Don't.
- Stay there.
- No. No, Mark, please. Don't leave me.
Oi! Come here!
Help him up!
- I'm critically injured, man.
- Let's take him upstairs.
I'm gonna deal with you later, boy!
Help him up.
Fuck, man! I need fucking...
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Shit.
Bandages.
Come on, something.
Come on, fuck's sake!
- We need to take it out.
- We need to leave it in.
- Listen, why don't you leave it in?
- It's all right. Calm down.
Focus.
- I'm turning the fucking lights on.
- He said no lights.
We need to see what we're doing.
- Fuck!
- Jesus!
Fuck!
He needs a doctor.
If we take him to the hospital,
we trash this entire plan.
Don't talk rubbish.
Nobody's leaving. I've had worse.
Now, do we have the family?
Taped and tacked.
They're not going anywhere.
They were all screaming
like a bunch of little girls.
Let's be clear.
Nobody used any real names.
- No, I don't think so.
- You better be sure.
I don't think so.
If they heard any names
we're gonna have to kill them.
Look, I didn't use any, did you?
- No.
- You sure?
There were no names.
Okay, we carry on. You two,
you do the business without me.
- We can do it.
- I should go too.
No. You're staying here. As before.
The whole thing stays the same,
only difference, you don't have
this fucker slowing you down.
I'm a big boy. I just have to wait
a couple of hours, don't I?
Call that dodgy quack, Fallon, yeah?
He'll come and patch me up.
After the work.
We could take you to him now
or just bring him here.
No! There's 27 million in that depot
today. Get him dressed for work.
We stick to the schedule.
You two come back here after the work.
You take me to him, after, okay? Yes?
We've done the hardest bit,
haven't we, Shane?
- No fucking names!
- Sorry.
- I should go to the depot.
- We stick to the schedule.
Now get him dressed for work.
Go to casualty...
recovery position...
A tourniquet?
How do you tie a tourniquet
around a stomach?
Stop the bleeding...
Oi! Someone get in here!
Look, it says here if we raise the wound
above the heart we can stop the bleeding.
I want to raise the bed. Come help me.
Come.
Get those books.
- Is that enough?
- Enough.
- On three.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
Wait. Wait.
The wife.
She's a doctor.
Give me some space. Stand over there.
I need boiling water
and towels cut into strips.
Now.
Okay. I'm gonna have to take this out.
- Leave it in.
- I'm a doctor.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Okay. Okay.
Fuck!
There's only so much I can do.
It's a deep puncture wound
and he's already lost a lot of blood.
There's internal bleeding and there may be
fragments of glass left in the wound.
You need my husband to help you, yes?
And you're holding me and my son
to ensure his compliance.
If this goes wrong...
we won't get out of here, will we?
Well, let's just hope that everything...
goes smoothly.
Do we still need to raise the bed?
Don't be ridiculous.
- I'll get rid of this.
- No!
It's all clean downstairs!
Look, me and my friend,
we're gonna do this job.
We're just not doing it
with your boy, okay?
- We're leaving here as planned.
- I said that, didn't I?
I just don't wanna work
with someone that I don't know.
Especially on the edge and I don't like
his attitude. I'm sorry.
I fucking said that, didn't I?
- I'm gonna need to take the shoe.
- This is planned. You stay here, okay?
Someone's got to take your place
and I'm stepping up.
His other half is doing it.
He's on the van.
You stay here. Do the scanner.
Watch the hostages as planned, okay?
Fuck!
You need to clean up the evidence we've
left behind. There's a lot of blood here.
- It's a mess.
- I ain't a cleaner.
It's not the score that's hard.
It's getting away with it.
Cleaning up is the most important part
of this job. We are all relying on you.
Get some bleach
and clean up every single drop.
This is bullshit!
- You don't trust me, no.
- My decision is made.
Hey!
Come here.
Hey. Hey. I don't want him to hear.
I'm old. I'm a scared old man.
I stood up for you.
I told them you'd be outstanding.
I said, "He is solid."
I can do this, Shane.
- I can.
- I know. I know.
That stretch straightened you out, boy.
It straightened you right out.
Just be grateful you don't have
to work up a sweat. I'm outta here.
- Slow and sure, control the room.
- You're the boss.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fan-fucking-tastic.
Go on with it.
- What's that?
- Accelerants.
Your DNA's all over the place.
No amount of bleach is gonna hide that.
The only way to do this properly
is to burn it down.
We'll soak the mattress. Do the lot.
You were always mad
for burning stuff up.
Hey, just you make sure
that I'm not here when you do it, yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
I should be in the front doing the job.
Your place is here.
We spent months planning this.
You're what, five weeks out?
I brought you in.
You should be thankful for that.
Why do you talk to me like a kid?
Somewhere quiet.
Middle of nowhere.
Stay in a B&B. Pay cash.
- Keep your head down for six months.
- What's this?
You know what I did first thing
when I got out?
I went to see Lucille.
You seen her lately?
No.
I haven't seen her for... years.
She's got a little one
as well, you know?
Beautiful little thing.
Yeah, my first fuck as a free man.
Nothing like it.
Go on, just pick up.
- Hello.
- Showtime. Everything good there?
All great. Start the clock.
Start the clock.
We're pulling up
to the security lodge now.
- You hear me all right?
- Loud and clear.
- You copy, Number 2?
- Yes, good. In position.
Yeah, we're good then?
Nothing on the scanner.
- Slow and sure.
- Approaching the security gate now...
Show your pass to the window, Doug.
That's it.
All right. We're through.
I'll take care of the guard.
- Excuse me, sir, can I have a word?
- Yes, Officer.
- Gate's open, we're going inside.
- Copy that. On my way.
- Come on, boy!
- Heading to the security room.
Stay in front there, Doug.
Remember this is just another day at work.
Can you try and look a little less nervous?
Are you all right, Mr Fairfield?
This... policeman,
he needs to speak with you...
- What's going on?
- Get down on the floor!
- No one gets hurt.
- Please do as he says.
They're holding my family.
Don't hit any alarms,
do everything he says.
Get on the floor!
Get your hands behind your back now!
- That's security taken care of.
- Ma'am, if you please. I'm coming in here.
You must secure all the staff.
Don't forget the staff.
And remember the personal alarms.
Don't let any of them against the walls.
- How many staff are on shift now?
- Just four or five.
You call them into the meeting room.
You sit them down.
Slow and sure.
Come on, let's do this.
Everybody down!
- Get on the floor!
- Stay calm or they'll kill us.
No problems, everyone.
Please, please, do as these men say.
They're holding my family.
Nobody go near the fucking
wall alarms... face to the floor!
Remember, it's the red bundles.
The red ones. The twenties...
Go for the red bundles.
The red bundles, yeah.
We know. We're the ones
that are doing all the hard work
while you guys are sitting on your arses
drinking tea over there.
Yeah, we're just excited,
we're excited here.
So you want to be in on the action?
I got a massive buzz on, man.
Let's get this moving!
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me? Hello?
Shit, we lost him.
Don't worry about it.
They're probably just busy. It's just...
They'll call when they're done.
You call them if you hear anything
on the scanner.
Okay.
We've just gotta hope it works.
Oh, my God!
Hey, hey!
We're gonna find something
to cut you free, okay?
Okay.
Mr Fairfield?
Come on!
Hello?
Just wait. Just wait.
Lynn?
Anybody home?
I'm coming up the stairs.
Lynn?
Oh, my God!
Would you say that you'd seen my face?
Who are you? What's going on here?
Lynn?
- It's gonna be an issue.
- What?
- I don't want to do this.
- Do what?
This!
Cover yourself up.
What have you done?
He's not gonna like this!
We're gonna call you...
Lover Boy.
Naughty boy?
You and me, boy...
We ain't finished.
You can't just go hitting people
with cricket bats.
Someone might get hurt.
No!
Don't!
What?
Help!
Someone, please!
Help me!
Fuck!
I thought you said you got rid of it.
Fucking thing messed up my life once.
You're gonna help me now.
No!
Fuck! Where's the bolt? Fuck!
Fuck! No! No!
Fuck.
Help!
Yeah?
No, he's fine.
No, nothing from the feds.
What's happening?
All right. See you soon.
Staff are locked in the vault.
They drove away with a fat lot.
We did it. We fucking did it.
Who's up there?
It's nothing. Got it covered.
You're gonna hurt her?
Look, just... close your eyes.
Think of the money.
Stop.
Stop. Stop! Stop!
I'm not gonna make it.
- Don't be silly. Of course you are.
- There's glass inside.
I can feel it tearing my insides.
Take me down. To the garden.
I need to see the garden.
You know, we can't do that.
Just try and rest, all right?
One, two, three.
You know, this time last month
I was inside.
2,164 days.
I ain't going back there again.
See, I went in 'cause of weakness.
I was robbing a house.
And some guy jumped out.
So, I cut him in his throat.
Which is all right.
But there was some kid watching...
the whole thing.
You know, I looked at him
and I thought...
"He's just a kid.
"He's harmless."
That was his testimony that put me away.
Just so you know...
I'm very motivated.
Bitch! Fucking bitch!
- I'm going to fucking kill you!
- Are you very frightened?
- Yeah.
- Wait till I get out!
I don't wanna die.
- That makes two of us.
- Shane, let me out!
He killed someone?
Answer me.
- Yeah.
- Who?
I don't know.
Let me out!
I watched his dad die.
We were best friends.
We served together.
Two tours.
He had cancer.
I watched him waste away.
Only in...
the later stages he was
begging to be finished.
There's no dignity there, I mean...
Fuck that.
Who wants that?
So in the end...
I put a pillow...
on his face.
It was a kindness.
- Let me out!
- It's all right.
He's not coming out for a while, is he?
I guess not.
Tell us a joke.
- What?
- Anything.
- I don't know any.
- Yeah, you do.
Please, don't think too hard.
It'll come.
Go.
There's two goldfish in a tank...
And...
one turns to the other and says...
"You drive, I'll do the gun."
All right.
All right, what?
Fuck off, then.
Shane, please!
No!
We need to go now. We need to go.
Stop, stop, stop.
Come here.
I'm frightened.
I've done questionable things.
Think about the people you love.
Come on.
- Get that.
- What are you talking about?
Officer, please help! Help!
He's upstairs, he's...
They're upstairs!
Get down on the ground! Face down!
Face down! Don't look at me!
- No, no, no...
- Take that fucking...
No, no!
Stupid fuck. He's locked in the attic.
Who?
- Shut up!
- No shit.
He says there is a girl as well.
Says she's seen his face.
She knows his name. Fuck!
Shut up!
Stay down!
So what are you saying?
Think about it. If that idiot gets caught,
he'll give us up for sure.
Leave him up there for now.
We have to take care of her.
- She's a little girl.
- I don't like it, either.
She's a little girl.
I'll look after her.
You take care of them.
Hey...
everybody dies.
You look like shit.
We cleaned the depot out.
No one has a clue. They won't for hours.
And it's all thanks to you.
That's great.
There is the girl we didn't
know about running around.
She knows too much.
What you pissing about here then for?
Just take the money and... and go.
There's a lady, a lady.
I want her looked after.
It's Lucille.
Don't kill Callum.
Lucille. It's done.
- You find her.
- I find her.
If you see the girl, you pop her.
Okay? You do it for us.
For the score.
- For Lucille.
- Just go. Go.
We had some good times.
You check upstairs. I'll look outside.
Think. Come on.
Who's there?
Open the hatch!
Open the hatch! Open the fucking hatch!
Who's down there?
Shane, open the hatch!
- Open the fucking hatch!
- I'm coming, man.
Fuck! Let me out!
- What the fuck you doing down there?
- Hang on.
- Let me out of here!
- Fucking, hang on, Callum.
Let me out!
For fuck's sake!
Come on!
Get me down!
Shut the fuck up...
- You killed the girl?
- She's fucking hiding somewhere.
What the fuck you doing here, then?
Sort it.
She's got a gun?
- Yeah, we've all got a gun.
- Shane won't allow it.
- Forget Shane, he's finished.
- Shane won't allow it!
You ain't got the balls
for this, have you?
And you do?
Give me the gun, I'll sort it.
Make yourself useful.
Start the fire.
We'll smoke her out.
How much did you get, by the way?
We had to use a forklift. A fuckload.
Good job.
Fuck!
Help! Help!
Help!
Please, please don't hurt me.
Who are you?
They're gonna kill you. Run!
Bloody mess!
The plan was perfect!
And you still ballsed it up.
Had to be you. I thought
you'd be trouble and I was right.
I took control.
I had to.
Wait. There's something
you should know...
There are cameras hidden all over
this house. There's one up there.
I've recorded all our conversations.
Now put that gun down!
All right.
It's as before.
Go play the victim, I'll take off.
And remember, I know exactly
how much money was in that vault.
And I want my cut hidden at the flop
as arranged, otherwise...
Done!
Luckily for you the fire will destroy
most of your mistakes.
First...
You'd better deal with that.
Stop!
- Please, keep calm!
- Don't move! Don't fucking move!
Oh, bloody Christ!
Look at this terrible, terrible mess.
Should have been so easy.
No one was meant to get hurt.
All I wanted to do was live out
my days on a nice boat.
No debts, no mortgages
and away from that psycho bitch
and that screw-up of a son.
This is your fault.
Now, Lynn...
There's no need
to point that thing at me.
You can trust me.
I don't know who to trust anymore.
We need to get out of here now.
Kelly, come on!
I can't fit anymore.
I can come with you. We could go to Rio.
Is that what you really want?
I don't know.
You were right.
You've got a future ahead of you.
And... and now, I do too.
Come on, you've got to go now!
- Okay. Go over the story.
- We were tied up,
we didn't see anything,
the fight broke out against them.
A fire started but we managed to get out
in time and you were never here.
But... what about the...
Mark, Kelly knows what she's doing.
We'll be fine.
I promise.
Bye.
www.YTS.AG